campusbookrentals.com 2016-06-29

# Rent a Text Book | Textbook Privacy Policy | Campus Book Rentals

**Effective 8 April 2009**  
Updated 25 August 2015 

This privacy policy applies to <http://campusbookrentals.com/> owned and operated by Campus Book Rentals, Inc. (“Campus Book RentalsTM”, “we”, “us”, “our”). This privacy policy describes how Campus Book Rentals, Inc. collects and uses the personally identifiable information you provide on our web site: <http://campusbookrentals.com/>. 

Campus Book Rentals, Inc. has received TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, <http://campusbookrentals.com/>. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

Campus Book Rentals™, is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This document discloses the privacy practices for www.CampusBookRentals.com™ including: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Campus Book Rental's™ control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to Campus Book Rentals™ via email. See our contact us page. 

**Table of Contents**   
1\. Minors   
2\. Information We Collect   
3\. Our Use of Your Information   
4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information 

5\. Control of Your Password   
6\. Single Sign-on 7\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information   
8\. Other Information Collectors   
9\. Security   
10\. Changes to Privacy Policy 

**1\. Minors**   
Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under 18 years of age) do not submit any personally identifiable information to us. We understand that minors attend universities and require textbooks. We ask that the legal guardian complete the registration and rental process on behalf of the minor. 

**2\. Information We Collect**   
Our primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and personalized experience while using our services. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker. 

To fully use our services, you will need to register where you will be required to provide us with the following personally identifiable information:

  * Name
  * Shipping Address
  * Billing Address
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information
  * School Information

** Collection of 3rd party Personally Identifiable Information  **   
You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, date of birth and gender. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided. 

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

NOTE: Participant may also link to the NAI opt-out mechanism <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

** Tracking Technologies  **   
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Campus Book Rentals, Inc. and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics, and online service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for certain marketing campaigns (like retargeting) and authenticating affiliate-referral sales. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

** Log Files  **   
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

**Google AdSense/AdWords**   
We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

**Links to 3rd Party Sitess**   
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Campus Book Rentals, Inc. If you submit personally identifiable information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

**Surveys, Contests, Testimonials**   
From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys, contests or for a particular service (e.g. testimonial). Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested will include contact information (as supplied to the site during registration) and supplementary information on your opinions, feedback, testimonials, etc. In the event of a contest, we will use the contact information to notify winners. We will not publish winners' details on the site. If the survey or contest has a sponsor then we will share information given by entrants with the sponsor. 

**Payment Policies**   
In order to process payments online we require the billing address for the credit card used and our external payment provider, Internet Secure, requires your credit card number and details. This is all done on a secure Internet Secure server using SSL (secure sockets layer) technology. For additional information on Internet Secure, logon to www.internetsecure.com and read their terms and conditions and policies.

**Customer Names and Shipping Addresses**   
CampusBookRentals.com uses third party providers to package and deliver books to its customers. Customer names and shipping addresses are shared with our suppliers and shipping providers in order to complete the delivery process. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Refer-A-Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. CampusBookRentals.com does not store this information.

**3\. Our Use of Your Information**   
We use personally identifiable information about you to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. 

We use your e-mail address to communicate order information to you and to provide you with other communications or information that you have requested from CampusBookRentals.com.

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve any disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Service Policy and Rental Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular on rare occasions we may evaluate your information to look for users using multiple User IDs or alias. 

**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**   
Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or 

_comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process_

served on our website. 

As a general proposition, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 

If CampusBookRentals.com™ is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

**Legal Requests**   
CampusBookRentals.com™ cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. Local, and international law enforcement agents can request and may receive your personally identifiable information. 

**5\. Control of Your Password**   
Except as specifically permitted by this section, you may not disclose your CampusBookRentals.com™ password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password by visiting the login page on the Site. 

If you wish to change your password you can do so at any time through the 'Edit Profile' section of the site. 

**6\. Single Sign-on**   
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**7\. Reviewing, Changing and Deleting Your Personally Identifiable Information**   
You can at any time review and change the information you submitted during registration by visiting the login page on the site.

You must promptly update your information if it changes. Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in our forums or other message areas or the feedback area through your account. If you no longer desire our services you may ask to have your account deactivated or ask to have your information deleted/removed from public postings made in our forums or other message areas or the feedback area by emailing us at [info@campusbookrentals.com](mailto:info@campusbookrentals.com). We will respond to your request to access in 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide your services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**8\. Other Information Collectors**   
Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are other members of the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you disclose to them.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**9\. Security**   
In order to process and protect your credit card details, our payment provider, Internet Secure uses SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption. The secure server is hosted by a third-party service and not CampusBookRentals.com™. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**10\. Changes to Privacy Policy**   
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email (sent to the email address specified in your account), prior to making such changes. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice, before changes go into effect, on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Corporate Office Physical Address**   
224 S 200 W #100  
Salt Lake City, UT 84101

**Distribution Facility Physical Address**   
2805 S 1900 W   
Ogden, UT 84401

**Email address**
